Finding Aid for Horace H. Rackham and Mary A. Rackham Fund Records 1929-1950
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Project applications/grants 1934-1942
  - Constantinople Woman's Club (Box 6)
  - Consultation Bureau, Detroit (Box 6)
  - Convent of the Felican Sisters (Box 6)
  - Convent of the Good Shepherd, Detroit (Box 6)
  - Cooley Foundation (Box 6)
  - Cornell, A.B (Box 6)
  - Council of City Teachers' Association of Ohio (Box 6)
  - Council of Social Agencies, Detroit (Box 6)
  - County and township reorganization problems (Box 6)
  - Courtois, Flora Simms (Box 6)
  - Cox, Joseph I (Box 6)
  - Craddock, Mrs. Eulalia (Box 7)
  - Cradle Society, Chicago (Box 7)
  - Crowell Memorial Home (Box 7)
  - Curry, Arthur (Box 7)
  - Curry, Mrs. Ira (Box 7)
  - Curtis, Florence (Box 7)
  - D miscellaneous (Box 7)
  - Danby, Mrs. Grace (Box 7)
  - Darling, John (Box 7)
  - Davis, L. Leroy (Box 7)
  - Davis, R.E (Box 7)
  - Debo, Alfred, Lansing (Box 7)
  - Delaware County Medical Society (Box 7)
  - Department of Public Health, Sacramento, Calif (Box 7)
  - Detroit Artists Market (Box 7)
  - Detroit Association for the Deaf (Box 7)
  - Detroit Baptist Missionary Society (Box 7)
  - Detroit Board of Education (Box 7)
  - Detroit Board of Education, camps for boys, 3 folders (Box 7)
  - Detroit Citizens League (Box 7)
  - Detroit Community Fund, 3 folders (Box 7)
  - Detroit Consumptive and Ex-patient Relief Sanitorium (Box 7)
  - Detroit Council of Camp Fire Girls (Box 7)
  - Detroit Council of Churches (Box 7)
  - Detroit Council of Youth Service, Sanders (Box 7)
  - Detroit District Dental Society (Box 7)
  - Detroit Episcopal City Mission (Box 7)
  - Detroit Federation of Women's Clubs (Box 7)
  - Detroit Free Press Fresh Air Fund (Box 7)
  - Detroit High School and College Scholarship Association (Box 7)
  - Detroit Historical Society (Box 7)
  - Detroit Independent School Association (Box 7)
  - Detroit Institute of Arts, 3 folders (Box 7)
  - Detroit League for the Handicapped (Box 7)
  - Detroit League for the Hard of Hearing (Box 7)
  - Detroit Orthopedic Clinic (Box 7)
  - Detroit Public Library Commission, Detroit Historical Society (Box 7)
  - Detroit Public Library Commission, Medical Science Dept (Box 7)
  - Detroit Social Hygiene Conference (Box 7)
  - Detroit Symphony Society, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Detroit Urban League (Box 7)
  - Detroit Zoological Park, 2 folders (Box 7)
    (includes files re: Rackham Fountain with photographs)
  - Diehl, H.S., University of Minnesota (Box 7)
  - Dodge, Percival (Box 8)
  - Dodge Community House, Detroit (Box 8)
  - Dominican Sisters of the Sick Poor (Box 8)
  - Donald Whaley Home, Flint (Box 8)
  - Donnelly, Leo (Box 8)
  - Downtown School for Delinquents, Oklahoma (Box 8)
  - Dudding, Earl Ellicott, Prisoners Relief Society (Box 8)
  - Duke University (Box 8)
  - Dunbar Association, Inc (Box 8)
  - Dunbar Memorial Hospital (Box 8)
  - Duniven, Grace Votaw (Box 8)
  - E miscellaneous (Box 8)
  - Ecker, E.E (Box 8)
  - Education (Box 8)
  - Education and Law Conference (Box 8)
  - Edwin Gould Foundation for Children (Box 8)
  - Elder, Mrs. George (Box 8)
  - Eldredge, Edwin (Box 8)
  - Ellison, John V (Box 8)
  - Elyria Home for the Aged, Elyria, Ohio (Box 8)
  - Emery, Frank B (Box 8)
  - Emmaus Home (Box 8)
  - Emory and Henry College (Box 8)
  - England, Howell S (Box 8)
  - Episcopal Church Home, Washington D.C (Box 8)
  - Epstean, George (Box 8)
  - Evangelical Lutheran Old Folks Home, Monroe, Mich (Box 8)
  - Evangelical Lutheran Samaritan Church (Box 8)
  - Evans, Mabel Lawrence (Box 8)
  - Evans, W.A., Harper Hospital, Detroit (Box 8)
  - Evans Clinic Association (Box 8)
  - Ever Loyal Business Men's Willing Workers (Box 8)
  - F miscellaneous (Box 8)
  - Fackler, Paul A., Detroit Chiropractic Hospital (Box 8)
  - Farrand Training School for Nurses (Box 8)
  - Faulk, Robert W (Box 8)
  - Federal Council of Churches (Box 8)
  - Federal Council of Church of Christ in America (Box 8)
  - Fenton, Mich., 6 folders (Box 8)
  - Ferris Institute (Box 8)
  - Field, Mrs. Clara (Box 8)
  - Fields, Charles (Box 8)
  - Fields, Mrs. Emma (Box 8)
  - Finnish Relief Society, Inc (Box 8)
  - Fireside Fellowship League (Box 8)
  - First Baptist Church, Bay City, Mich (Box 8)
  - First Bapitist Church, Nashville, Tenn (Box 8)
  - First Christian Church, Dayton, Ky (Box 8)
  - First Church of Christ, Scientist, Detroit (Box 8)
  - First Friends Church, Detroit (Box 8)
  - First Methodist Episcopal Church, Fenton, Mich (Box 8)
  - First Missionary Baptist Church (Box 8)
  - Flint Chamber Music Society (Box 8)
  - Flint Endowment for Sociology (Box 8)
  - Flint Institute of Art (Box 8)
  - Flint Institute of Research and Planning, 1 volumes; 1 folders (Box 8)
  - Flint Project (Box 8)
  - Flint Sociological Research Endowment (Box 8)
  - Florence Crittenton Hospital (Box 8)
  - Flushing, Mich (Box 8)
  - Foreign Language Information Service, New York City (Box 8)
  - Fort Bethold Indian Mission (Box 8)
  - Fourth Church of Christ, Scientist, Detroit (Box 8)
  - Fox, Merle A (Box 8)
  - Frances Willard Home (Box 8)
  - Frank, Lawrence K (Box 8)
  - Franklin Settlement, Detroit, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Franklin Settlement Camps (Box 9)
  - Friend of the Court (Box 9)
  - Fries, E.J (Box 9)
  - Fries, Mrs. Rhoda M (Box 9)
  - Frontier Nursing Service (Box 9)
  - Fulford, Cora (Box 9)
  - Fuller, Floyd H (Box 9)
  - G miscellaneous (Box 9)
  - General Reduction Corporation (Box 9)
  - Generaux, George (Box 9)
  - Generaux, Walter (Box 9)
  - Geneva College (Box 9)
  - George Peabody College for Teachers (Box 9)
  - Georgetown College (Box 9)
  - Georgia Warm Springs Foundation (Box 9)
  - German-Protestant Home for Orphans and Aged (Box 9)
  - Gibson, T.T (Box 9)
  - Gilbert Wilkes Camp, no. 17, United Spanish War Veterans (Box 9)
  - Gillespie, Glenn C (Box 9)
  - Gingling College, Nanking, China (Box 9)
  - Girl Scouts (Box 9)
  - Gold Rule Foundation (Box 9)
  - Golden Age Training School and Encampment for Christian Workers (Box 9)
  - Gonne, William S (Box 9)
  - Good Samaritan Clinic, Atlanta, Ga (Box 9)
  - Goodfellow's Old Newsboys Fund, Detroit (Box 9)
  - Goodger, Mrs. Arthur (Box 9)
  - Goodrich, B.E (Box 9)
  - Goodwill Industries of Detroit, Inc (Box 9)
  - Gorman, Michael A (Box 9)
  - Gordon, William H (Box 9)
  - Grace Hospital, Detroit (Box 9)
  - Grace Presbyterian Church, Detroit (Box 9)
  - Grand Rapids Art Gallery (Box 9)
  - Grand River Baptist Church (Box 9)
  - Green Cross Nurse Association (Box 9)
  - Grosse Pointe Neighborhood Club (Box 9)
  - Guckert, Elroy S (Box 9)
  - Gurnea, Mrs. Grace (Box 9)
  - H miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Hallowell-Wellington Kindergarten (Box 9)
  - Hamilton, Mrs. Chester (Box 9)
  - Handicap Co-operative, Detroit (Box 9)
  - Handicapped (Box 9)
  - Handicraft, Inc (Box 9)
  - Handy Home for Old People (Box 9)
  - Hannan (Luella) Memorial Home (Box 9)
  - Hardwick, Ella (Box 9)
  - Harmon Association for the Advancement of Nursing (Box 9)
  - Harper Hospital, Detroit (Box 9)
  - Harrington, Mrs. Charles (Box 9)
  - Harrington, Mrs. Grace (Box 9)
  - Harris, Reba (Box 9)
  - Harvard College (Box 9)
  - Haven Hubbard Memorial Old People's Home (Box 9)
  - Haven, Rochester, Mich (Box 9)
  - Hayes, J.J (Box 9)
  - Hazel Park Exchange Club, Royal Oak, Mich (Box 9)
  - Healy, Mrs. Mabel (Box 9)
  - Heaney's Grand Rapids Commercial College (Box 9)
  - Hearing House, YMCA (Box 9)
  - Heath, Parker (Box 9)
  - Hebrew Convalescent Home (Box 9)
  - Helping Hand Home (Box 9)
  - Henshaw, Dorothy (Box 9)
  - Hessler, Robert (Box 9)
  - Hickey (Paul) Foundation (Box 9)
  - Highland Park Community Center (Box 9)
  - Highland Park Woman's Club Camp (Box 9)
  - Hinrichs, William E (Box 9)
  - Hoffman, Wallace (Box 9)
  - Horton, B.D (Box 9)
  - Horton, Hadley (Box 9)
  - Horton, Mrs. Ruby (Box 9)
  - Horton, Walter (Box 9)
  - Houghton, Mrs. Catherine (Box 9)
  - Houghton, Elmer (Box 9)
  - Houghton, Florence Teats (Box 9)
  - Houghton, William (Box 9)
  - Howard Street Rescue Mission, Inc (Box 9)
  - Howe, Martha (Box 9)
  - Huggins, Luella (Box 9)
  - Hunt, Matilda (Box 9)
  - Huntington College (Box 9)
  - Hurley Hospital (Box 9)
  - Hurst, Daniel (Box 9)
  - I-J miscellaneous (Box 9)
  - Indian missions, Northern Michigan (Box 9)
  - Industrial morale and personnel problems (Box 9)
  - Industrial science (Box 9)
  - Infantile paralysis (Box 10)
  - Ingham County Project for Speech Defects (Box 10)
  - Ingram, Mrs. R.A (Box 10)
  - Inquiries (Box 10)
  - Institute of Women's Professional Relations, New London, Conn (Box 10)
  - International Association of Chiefs of Police (Box 10)
  - International Migration Service, Inc (Box 10)
  - International Music Festival, Detroit (Box 10)
  - International Save the Child Fund, New York (Box 10)
  - Iodized Salt Company (Box 10)
  - Italian Baptist Church of Our Savior (Box 10)
  - James DeWitt Auxiliary no. 38, American Legion (Box 10)
  - Jardon, Marta (Box 10)
  - Jefferson Avenue Baptist Church, Detroit (Box 10)
  - Jefferson Medical College (Box 10)
  - Johnson, Benton V (Box 10)
  - Johnson, Sadie (Box 10)
  - Joint Committee on Public Health Administration (Box 10)
  - Joint Vocational Service, Inc., New York (Box 10)
  - Jordan College (Box 10)
  - Judicial Council of Michigan (Box 10)
  - Junior Programs, Inc., New York (Box 10)
  - K miscellaneous (Box 10)
  - Kahn, Reuben (Box 10)
  - Kalamazoo College (Box 10)
  - Kalamazoo Sea Scout Squadron (Box 10)
  - Kelleher, Mrs. Jennie (Box 10)
  - Kellogg (W.K.) Foundation (Box 10)
  - Kent County Board of School Examiners (Box 10)
  - Kentucky Female Orphan School (Box 10)
  - King's Daughter and Sons (Box 10)
  - Kingswood College (Box 10)
  - Knight Menard Company (Box 10)
  - Knighthood of Youth, National Child Welfare Association (Box 10)
  - Korzybski, Alfred (Box 10)
  - L miscellaneous (Box 10)
  - Laboratory of Anthropology, Santa Fe, New Mexico (Box 10)
  - Lacy, Arthur (Box 10)
  - Lappin, A.C (Box 10)
  - Larkins, Harriet (Box 10)
  - Lawrence Institute of Technology (Box 10)
  - League of Catholic Women (Box 10)
  - Leslie High School, Leslie, Mich (Box 10)
  - Lewis, Mrs. Florence R (Box 10)
  - Lewis Institute, Detroit (Box 10)
  - Lichtwardt, H.A., American Hospital, Hamadan, Persia (Box 10)
  - Lincoln Memorial University (Box 10)
  - Lindsley, Mrs. Emily (Box 10)
  - Lions Club of Detroit (Box 10)
  - Little, Andrew (Box 10)
  - Little Flower Crusade, Crippled children (Box 10)
  - Livingstone College (Box 10)
  - Losee, M.A (Box 10)
  - Louisiana State University (Box 10)
  - Louisville and Jefferson County Children's Home (Box 10)
  - Lutheran Children Friend Society (Box 10)
  - M miscellaneous (Box 10)
  - Mc miscellaneous (Box 10)
  - Macy, Frederick S (Box 10)
  - Macy (Josiah, Jr.) Foundation (Box 10)
  - Major, Mrs. Cortland (Box 10)
  - Malseedee, John H (Box 10)
  - Mason, Mich (Box 10)
  - Matel, Joe (Box 10)
  - Matthews, John A (Box 10)
  - Maternal Health League of Michigan (Box 10)
  - McGuire, C.E (Box 10)
  - McLean, Angus (Box 10)
  - McMath-Hulbert Observatory (Box 10)
  - Mead, Mrs. J.E (Box 10)
  - Medical Relief Committee (Box 10)
  - Medical research (Box 10)
  - Medical Service Bureau of the Wayne County Medical Society (Box 10)
  - Melville House (Box 10)
  - Mercy Hall Hospital (Box 10)
  - Mercywood Sanitarium (Box 10)
  - Meroff, Benny (Box 10)
  - Merrill-Palmer School, Detroit (Box 10)
  - Methodist Children's Home Society of Michigan, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Methodist Episcopal Church, Newberry, Mich (Box 10)
  - Michael, James (Box 11)
  - Michigan Association of Occupational Therapy (Box 11)
  - Michigan Child Guidance Institute (Box 11)
  - Michigan Children's Aid Society (Box 11)
  - Michigan Christian Endeavor Union (Box 11)
  - Michigan College of Mining and Technology (Box 11)
  - Michigan colleges (Box 11)
  - Michigan Cooperative League (Box 11)
  - Michigan Council of Churches (Box 11)
  - Michigan Council on Adult Education (Box 11)
  - Michigan Crippled Children Commission (Box 11)
  - Michigan Department of Health (Box 11)
  - Michigan Department of Public Instruction (Box 11)
  - Michigan Division of Rehabilitation (Box 11)
  - Michigan Farm Colony for Epileptics, Wahjamega, Mich (Box 11)
  - Michigan Home and Training School (Box 11)
  - Michigan Housing Commission (Box 11)
  - Michigan League, University of Michigan (Box 11)
  - Michigan League for Crippled Children (Box 11)
  - Michigan Municipal League, Olson (Box 11)
  - Michigan School for the Blind (Box 11)
  - Michigan Society for Crippled Children (Box 11)
  - Michigan Society for Mental Hygiene (Box 11)
  - Michigan State College, 5 folders (Box 11)
    (now Michigan State University)
  - Michigan State Normal College, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Michigan state parks (Box 11)
  - Michigan State Welfare Department (Box 11)
  - Michigan Tuberculosis Association (Box 11)
  - Michigan Works Progress Administration (Box 11)
  - Milligan College, 3 folders (Box 11)
  - Miner (John) Migratory Bird Foundation (Box 11)
  - Minkler, Mrs. Fred (Box 11)
  - Missionary Workers, Inc (Box 11)
  - Missouri Sunday School Council (Box 11)
  - Modern Missions Movement (Box 11)
  - Morgan, Mrs. Libbie (Box 11)
  - Moss, F.A (Box 11)
  - N miscellaneous (Box 11)
  - Narcotic Educational Association of Michigan (Box 11)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - National Association of Audubon Societies (Box 11)
  - National Child Welfare Association (Box 11)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene (Box 11)
  - National Committee of Bar Examiners (Box 12)
  - National Committee on Mental Health, Inc (Box 12)
  - National Committee on Prisons and Prison Labor (Box 12)
  - National Conference on Alcoholism (Box 12)
  - National Congress of Parents and Teachers (Box 12)
  - National Council for the Prevention of War (Box 12)
  - National Council on Religion in Higher Education (Box 12)
  - National Kindergarten Association (Box 12)
  - National League of Women Voters (Box 12)
  - National Municipal League (Box 12)
  - National Music Camp, Interlochen, Mich (Box 12)
  - National Organization for Public Health Nursing, New York (Box 12)
  - National Recreation Association, New York, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - National Tuberculosis Association (Box 12)
  - National Urban League, New York (Box 12)
  - Near East Foundation (Box 12)
  - Netzorg School of Piano (Box 12)
  - Newport County Osteopathic Clinic, Newport, R.I (Box 12)
  - New York Serbon (Box 12)
  - North Bennett Street Industrial School (Box 12)
  - Northeastern University (Box 12)
  - Northern Michigan Children's Clinic (Box 12)
  - Northrup, Frank (Box 12)
  - Northwestern Baptist Hospital Association (Box 12)
  - Northwestern University (Box 12)
  - Novy, Frederick G (Box 12)
  - Oakland Citizens League (Box 12)
  - Oakland County Department of Health, Pontiac (Box 12)
  - O'Connell, G.W (Box 12)
  - Ohio Radio Association (Box 12)
  - Old age relief (Box 12)
  - Old Newsboys Goodfellow Fund (Box 12)
  - Olivet College (Box 12)
  - Onstatt, Mrs. Daisey (Box 12)
  - Oriental Institute, University of Chicago (Box 12)
  - Osborne Associations, Inc (Box 12)
  - Outdoor swimming pool for children, Bay City, Mich (Box 12)
  - Owen Sound Health and Recreation Club (Box 12)
  - Oxford Mission to Calcutta (Box 12)
  - Ozark Mountain School (Box 12)
  - P miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - Parent Teacher Association (Box 12)
  - Parke, Mrs. Lurania (Box 12)
  - Pathfinders of America (Box 12)
  - Pattison, Lee (Box 12)
  - People's University Movement, Lansing, Mich (Box 12)
  - Perry, Fred (Box 12)
  - Perry, Mrs. Laura (Box 12)
  - Peterman, E.A (Box 12)
  - Pettibone, Mrs. Cora (Box 12)
  - Philadelphia Institute of Medical Research (Box 12)
  - Phillips, Mrs. Jennie (Box 12)
  - Phyllis Wheatley Home (Box 12)
  - Pontiac Board of Commerce (Box 12)
  - Pontiac City Library (Box 12)
  - Pontiac Union Rescue Mission (Box 12)
  - Pontiac Y.M.C.A. Community Center (Box 12)
  - Poos, Edgar E (Box 12)
  - Port Huron, Mich (Box 12)
  - Port Huron Welfare Camp (Box 12)
  - Port Huron Y.M.C.A (Box 12)
  - Presbyterian College of Christian Education (Box 12)
  - Principia Character Building School (Box 12)
  - Princeton University (Box 12)
  - Process engineering (Box 12)
  - Progressive Education Association Convention, Ann Arbor, Mich (Box 12)
  - Protestant Children's Home, Detroit (Box 12)
  - Public Welfare Association, New York (Box 12)
  - Pythagoras Foundation (Box 12)
  - R miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Rackham, Harry (Box 13)
  - Rackham, Ralph (Box 13)
  - Rackham, Virginia (Box 13)
  - Ramage, A.F (Box 13)
  - Recreation (Box 13)
  - Reed, Mrs. Ida (Box 13)
  - Religious Education Association (Box 13)
  - Rennsselear Polytechnic Institute (Box 13)
  - Renshaw, Mrs. Mary (Box 13)
  - Riemenschneider, L.E (Box 13)
  - Rigelman, William (Box 13)
  - Rively, Anna Emma (Box 13)
  - Robbins, Frank K (Box 13)
  - Rochester Historical Centennial (Box 13)
  - Rolland, Frederick (Box 13)
  - Rollins College (Box 13)
  - Rowe, Pauline (Box 13)
  - Rowland, Detroit, Mich (Box 13)
  - Royal Oak Public Library (Box 13)
  - Runyan, Mrs. Kate (Box 13)
  - Russell, Nelson Vance (Box 13)
  - Russell Sage Foundation (Box 13)
  - Ryan, Mrs. Ressie Teats (Box 13)
  - S miscellaneous (Box 13)
  - St. Andrew's Mission, Flint, Mich (Box 13)
  - St. John's Church, Toronto (Box 13)
  - St. Joseph Hospital (Box 13)
  - St. Joseph Mercy Hospital, Detroit (Box 13)
  - St. Joseph's Orphan Home (Box 13)
  - St. Luke's Convalenscent Home (Box 13)
  - St. Luke's Hospital (Box 13)
  - St. Marion's Church, Detroit (Box 13)
  - St. Mary's Hospital, Detroit (Box 13)
  - St. Paul A.M.E. Church (Box 13)
  - St. Paul's Methodist Episcopal Church (Box 13)
  - St. Theresa Orphan's Home (Box 13)
  - Saltzstein, Harry C (Box 13)
  - Salvation Army Summer Camp (Box 13)
  - School for Organic Education (Box 13)
  - School Social Service Committee (Box 13)
  - Schust, Gustave A (Box 13)
  - Scovil, Mrs. Jane (Box 13)
  - Seaman's Church Institute of New York (Box 13)
  - Secondary schools (Box 13)
  - Sergeant's Club, Inc., Detroit Area (Box 13)
  - Shady Trails Camp, Northport, Mich., 3 folders (Box 13)
  - Siefert, E.A (Box 13)
  - Sigma Gamma Clinic and Convalescent Hospital (Box 13)
  - Slater (John J.) Fund, Washington D.C (Box 13)
  - Smith, R.B (Box 13)
  - Smithies, Frank (Box 13)
  - Sober, Frederick James (Box 13)
  - Social service (Box 13)
  - Society for Economic Freedom, Detroit, Mich (Box 13)
  - Society of Arts and Crafts (Box 13)
  - Society of Good Neighbors (Box 13)
  - Sophie Wright Settlement (Box 13)
  - South Dakota State College (Box 13)
  - Southern Oakland Girl Scouts, Royal Oak, Mich (Box 14)
  - Spalding, Samuel (Box 14)
  - Sponsoring Committee for Subsistence Homesteads (Box 14)
  - Spring Arbor Seminary and Junior College (Box 14)
  - Starr Commonwealth for Boys (Box 14)
  - Stevens, C. Burton (Box 14)
  - Stevens, George (Box 14)
  - Stewart, Robert (Box 14)
  - Stout, Mrs. Harry, Jr (Box 14)
  - Student Christian Association, University of Michigan (Box 14)
  - Student Loan Fund, University of Michigan (Box 14)
  - Sugar, David I (Box 14)
  - Suttenfield, Maurine (Box 14)
  - Swedish National Sanitorium, Denver, Colo (Box 14)
  - T miscellaneous (Box 14)
  - Tanglewood School for Sub-normal Children (Box 14)
  - Teats, Phillip (Box 14)
  - Templin, August (Box 14)
  - Thompson Home for Old People (Box 14)
  - Tighe, O.P (Box 14)
  - Topping, Nettie (Box 14)
  - Travis, Ray C (Box 14)
  - Treadgold, A.N (Box 14)
  - Tufts College (Box 14)
  - Tuskegee Normal and Industrial Institute (Box 14)
  - Twentieth Century Fund, New York (Box 14)
  - United States Fire Protection Co., Providence, R.I (Box 14)
  - University of Chicago (Box 14)
  - University of Cincinnati (Box 14)
  - University of Detroit (Box 14)
  - University of Miami (Box 14)
  - Uplands Cumberland Mountain Sanitorium (Box 14)
  - Upper Canada Tract Society Sailors' Home (Box 14)
  - Upson, Lent D (Box 14)
  - U-V miscellaneous (Box 14)
  - Van DeMark, Gloria (Box 14)
  - Vaughn, Henry F (Box 14)
  - Vineland (N.J.) Training School (Box 14)
  - Visiting Nurses Association, Pontiac, Mich (Box 14)
  - Visual method piano instructions (Box 14)
  - Volunteer Rescue Army, Inc., Detroit (Box 14)
  - W miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Wade, Mabel Generaux (Box 14)
  - Walther League Hospice, Detroit (Box 14)
  - Washington Cathedral (Box 14)
  - Washtenaw County Recreational Survey Program (Box 14)
  - Watson, C. Roy (Box 14)
  - Watson, Glenn (Box 14)
  - Wayne City Medical Society (Box 14)
  - Wayne County Fraternal Home Association (Box 14)
  - Wayne University (Box 14)
  - Wedda, Patricia (Box 14)
  - Weisflog, William (Box 14)
  - Wells, Harry L (Box 14)
  - Whiting, Andrew J (Box 14)
  - Whiting, Hattie (Box 14)
  - Wildman, H.A (Box 14)
  - Wilkerson, Mrs. Charlotte (Box 14)
  - Williams High School, Oakland, Mich (Box 14)
  - Williams House, Inc., Detroit (Box 14)
  - Winglemire, Mrs. J (Box 14)
  - Winkler, Ann Willard (Box 14)
  - Winters, Mrs. Ernest (Box 14)
  - Wolverines, Inc (Box 14)
  - Woman's Christian Temperance Union (Box 14)
  - Woman's Hospital, Detroit (Box 14)
  - Women's Civic League (Box 14)
  - Women's Committee of the Bonstelle Civic Theatre (Box 14)
  - Workers Education Bureau (Box 14)
  - World Adventure Series, Inc., Detroit Institute of Arts (Box 14)
  - World Civilization Conference (Box 14)
  - World Federation of Education Associations (Box 14)
  - Wright, Prudence (Box 14)
  - Wright Memorial Hospital, Alma, Mich (Box 14)
  - Wyer, S.S (Box 14)
  - Young, Mattie (Box 14)
  - Young Men's Christian Association, Detroit (Box 14)
  - Young Woman's Club of Detroit (Box 14)
  - Young Women's Christian Association (Box 14)
  - Youth, Inc (Box 14)
  - Ypsilanti, Mich (Box 14)